<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">cardsagainstyourliver</string>
    <string name="create_profile_text">create Profile</string>
    <string name="player_choice_text">Player selection</string>
    <string name="manual_text">Manual</string>
    <string name="play_text">Games</string>
    <string name="more_games_text">More Games</string>
    <string name="specialMode_text">Special mode</string>
    <string name="profiles_text">Profiles</string>
    <string name="profile_text">Profile</string>
    <string name="settings_text">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_text">Menu</string>
    <string name="startGame_text">Play</string>
    <string name="giveUp_text">Surrender</string>
    <string name="players_text">Player</string>
    <string name="player_01_text">Player 1</string>
    <string name="player_02_text">Player 2 +</string>
    <string name="youAre...">Your turn...</string>
    <string name="test_text">Play</string>
    <string name="age_text">Age</string>
    <string name="size_text">Height</string>
    <string name="bodyweight_text">Weight</string>
    <string name="gender_text">Gender</string>
    <string name="drink_text">Drink</string>
    <string name="age_hint">Years</string>
    <string name="male_text">Female</string>
    <string name="female_text">Male</string>
    <string name="drink_01">Beer</string>
    <string name="drink_02">Wine</string>
    <string name="drink_09">Sparkling Wine</string>
    <string name="drink_11">Wheat Yeast</string>
    <string name="sound_off_text">Mute</string>
    <string name="sound_on_text">Sound on</string>
    <string name="placeholder_text">Placeholder</string>
    <string name="profilName_hint">enter Profilename</string>
    <string name="profileName_01_text">Profile_a</string>
    <string name="gameManual_text_Schwimmen">Manual: Schwimmen</string>
    <string name="gameManual_text_Bettler">Manual: Bettler</string>
    <string name="gameRules_text_Schwimmen">Rules: Schwimmen</string>
    <string name="rules_Schwimmen">The game \"Swimming\" is played with a single package of double German or French cards with 32 sheets, a so-called Skat sheet. The order is set clockwise. When it is a player\'s turn, he tries to establish a certain combination in his own hand by swapping playing cards. The goal in the game is not to end up with the combination that has the lowest point value.  Game objective and scoring But there are many different ways of creating a so-called combination. For example, you either collect cards of the same color and add their point values ​​- similar to the card game forty-one - where the following applies:  The ace gives eleven points The jack, queen and king are each worth ten points The number cards seven, eight, nine and ten count as much as their eyes (i.e. 7, 8,9 and 10 points) The maximum possible number of points in this case is 31, which is the case when a hand consists of an ace and two picture cards or an ace and a picture and a ten of the same suit.  However, it is also a good idea to combine cards of the same rank. This means that there is a combination, for example, of 3 sevens, three queens or three jacks - although these of course have different colors. A combination of this kind always counts for 30 and a half points. Individual examples for the scoring: Some examples are listed below to clarify the scoring. This makes it easier to familiarize yourself with the rules - especially if you\'ve never played a similar game. Here are the examples:  Queen of Hearts, Ten of Hearts, Jack of Diamonds: If a player has these cards in his hand, the corresponding combination is worth 20 points. The score is made up of 2 × 10 points, as the combination of the same color counts, and this is only the case with the Queen of Hearts and the Ten of Hearts. King of Clubs, Nine of Clubs, Ace of Clubs: This combination consists of three cards of the same suit. The ace counts 11, the king 10 and the nine counts 9. This gives a total of 30 points for this combination. Seven of Hearts, Seven of Spades, Seven of Diamonds: This combination contains three cards of the same rank. Therefore she counts 30 and a half cards. If several players can show this combination, i.e. a so-called tie occurs, the hand of the player with the highest rank counts. A sequence of three nines would proceed accordingly to the sequence of three sevens. King of Diamonds, Ace of Diamonds, Ten of Diamonds: This is a combination that counts 31 points: the ace gives 11 points, the king of diamonds gives 10 points, as does the ten of diamonds.</string>
    <string name="manual_Schwimmen">In the open game, the dealer deals three cards face down and individually to all players; to himself he hands out two packs of three cards each, also face down. The dealer then looks at the cards in one of the two stacks and must now make a decision. In this decision he has the choice whether he wants to play with the sighted cards or not. If he does not want to play with the cards from the first pile, these three cards are placed face up in the middle of the table. The dealer must now play with the cards in the second pile. However, if he wants to play with the cards from the first pile, the second pile is placed face up in the middle of the table. The remaining cards are now set aside. The player sitting to the left of the dealer is entitled to start the game. He can decide whether to swap either one or all three cards from his hand with the cards in the middle. It is not possible to swap two cards. If he does not want to swap, he signals this either with his statement “I\'m pushing!” Or he closes the game by knocking. All you need to do is knock your knuckles on the table. In the region it may also be common to say “I\'m closing” instead of knocking.  the end of the game There are two different ways to end the game:  If a player has 31 points, a so-called “thirty-one”, “Schnauz”, “Knack” or “Hosn obi”, he immediately puts the corresponding cards face up and visible to all on the table. The game is now over in an instant. In purely theoretical terms, it is possible in this sense that the game can end immediately after the cards have been dealt. If a player says \"I\'ll close\" or if he knocks, the other players are allowed to swap one more time. Then the game is over. It is common to play this game over several rounds. The loser is determined as follows: The player or players who have the least number of points in the form of card combinations at the end of the game are considered the loser.</string>
    <string name="gameRules_text_Bettler">Rules: Bettler</string>
    <string name="rules_Bettler">The rules vary widely. Therefore, it is important to determine these before starting the game. Up to seven players play with a standard 32 card game. For longer fun it is also possible to play with a rummy sheet or two standard card games.  At the beginning all cards are dealt equally face down to the players. Whoever holds the previously determined starting card (usually the seven of diamonds) is the first to play.  A single card or multiple cards can be played. Cards of the same value are called multiple cards.  For example  It is the turn of the other players to turn. You can pass or take the trick with a higher card. In multiples, the trick can only be taken with the same number of cards of a higher rank. This means that if there is a multiple of three nines on the table, the trick can only be taken with three tens, jacks, queens, kings or aces. The jokers can be an exception here. The use and rank of jokers must also be discussed beforehand.  It may be that it makes strategic sense to pass when you could take the trick. So there is no stitch duty. The player who took the trick comes out next.  The game round is over when the penultimate player runs out of cards. The last player with cards in hand is the asshole. If you are the first to have no more cards in hand, you become king of the round.  In many variants, the seating arrangement now changes according to the level of the offices won. The asshole is now the dealer because the loser begins the new round.  In this round cards are “pressed”. This means that players with low office must give their highest cards to players with higher office. The king gets the highest cards from the asshole in exchange for his lowest. The same is done with the other offices. Vice-asshole trades with vice-king and so on. This should definitely be discussed beforehand. Most of the variants stipulate that the asshole doesn\'t have to give up any aces.  If a card that has already been played is picked up again or if the set rules are violated in any other way, this player automatically becomes an asshole. The last player with cards in hand is just a runner-up asshole. If the last card is an ace, that player is automatically the asshole too. It is therefore important to pay attention to strategy in this fun game too.</string>


    <string name="invest_profile_text">create Profile</string>
    <string name="switch_text">change</string>
    <string name="life_text">Life :</string>
    <string name="your_turn_text">your turn!</string>
    <string name="now_player_text">your turn!</string>
    <string name="player_win_text">has won!</string>
    <string name="choice_cards_text">choose your Cards!</string>
    <string name="games_comming_soon">more games will follow...</string>
    <string name="resume_text">Resume</string>
    <string name="name_text2">name</string>
    <string name="continue_text">continue</string>
    <string name="schwimmen_has_ended">has finished!</string>
    <string name="schwimmen_has_closed">has pushed!</string>


    <string name="newGame_text">New Game</string>
    <string name="promille_text">permille</string>
    <string name="you_have_to_drink">take a sip!</string>
    <string name="nobody">Nobody</string>
    <string name="push">Push to</string>
    <string name="pushBettler">Push to</string>
    <string name="start">starts</string>
    <string name="is_king">is king!</string>
    <string name="choose_card">Please choose a card!</string>
    <string name="same_cards">You have to lay as many cards as your opponent!</string>
    <string name="higher_cards">The selected cards must be higher, see instructions!</string>
    <string name="same_cards2">Only cards of the same rank can be put together!</string>
    <string name="begins">begins!</string>
    <string name="give_card">hand in a card of your choice.</string>

</resources>